http://www.actfax.com/en/terms.html

Select your language
English (Englisch)
German (Deutsch)
7
You need to send documents from individual applications by fax?
Use ActFax to send faxes from any Windows application. It's as easy as printing.
You want a faxing solution that is easy to install and maintain?
ActFax is installed and configured in just a few minutes. Also if you are no IT expert.
Faxes should be automatically sent directly from your applications?
ActFax seamlessly integrates into all your applications. Quick and straightforward.
Received faxes should be automatically delivered to your users?
ActFax routes incoming faxes directly to your users. Fully automatically.
Always keeping track of the status of your fax messages is important for you?
ActFax notifies you by email or through the client software. In a matter of seconds.
The transmission of fax messages should be done through Voice over IP?
Use ActFax in combination with XCAPI. That's the future of faxing.
The reliability of your faxing solution is important for you?
More than 250,000 users worldwide trust in ActFax. Day by day.
4
the professional faxing solution
trusted by more than 250,000 users worldwide
easy to install and maintain
fast. reliable. scaleable.
Terms of Use
Welcome to the ActFax Communication Web site (the "Site"). By using
the Site, you agree to follow and be bound by the following terms and conditions
concerning your use of the Site ("Terms of Use") and our Privacy Policy. We may
revise the Terms of Use and Privacy Statement at
any time without notice to you.
Areas of the Site may have different terms of use posted. If there is a conflict
between the Terms of Use and terms of use posted for a specific area of the Site,
the latter shall have precedence with respect to your use of that area of the Site.
1. Use of Web Site Information
You may download, view, copy and print documents and graphics incorporated in
these documents (the "Documents") from the Site subject to the following: (a) the
Documents may be used solely for personal, informational, non-commercial purposes;
and (b) the Documents may not be modified or altered in any way. Except where your
use constitutes "fair use" under copyright law, you may not otherwise use, download,
upload, copy, print, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, post, transmit or
distribute any information from this Web site in whole or in part without the
express authorization of ActFax Communication.
2. Use of Software
Any use of software and accompanying documentation you download from the Site is
subject to the terms of a software license agreement between you and ActFax Communication. You must
read the license agreement and indicate your agreement to its terms prior to installing
or using the software. All rights, title and interest not expressly granted are reserved.
3. Use of Forums and Public Communication
"Forum" means a discussion group, chat area, bulletin board, news group, letter to
ActFax Communication, its webmaster or employees, or e-mail function offered as part of the Site. You
agree not to upload, email, post, publish or otherwise transmit through a Forum any
content that: (a) is false or misleading; (b) is defamatory; (c) is harassing or invades
another's privacy, or promotes bigotry, racism, hatred or harm against any group or
individual; (d) is obscene; (e) infringes another's rights, including but not limited
to intellectual property rights; (f) constitutes unsolicited bulk e-mail, "junk mail", "spam"
or chain letters; or (g) violates any applicable laws or regulations.
Forums shall be used in a noncommercial manner only. You shall not distribute or
otherwise publish any content containing a solicitation of funds, promotion, advertising,
solicitation for goods or services, or other commercial matter. You agree not to solicit
other users of the Site to use or join or become members of any commercial online or
offline service or other organization. Except where expressly authorized by ActFax Communication, you
agree not to collect or store personal data about other users.
By uploading, emailing, posting, publishing or otherwise transmitting content to any
Forum or submitting any content to ActFax Communication, you automatically grant (or warrant that the
owner of such rights has expressly granted) ActFax Communication a perpetual, royalty-free, irrevocable,
nonexclusive right and license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, transmit and
distribute such content on in any form, medium, or technology now known or later
developed. In addition, you warrant that all so-called moral rights in the content have
been waived.
4. Passwords and Security
You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any password(s) you are
given to access the Site, and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under
your password(s). You agree to notify ActFax Communication immediately of any unauthorized use of
your password(s).
ActFax Communication is concerned about the security of personal information we have collected
from you and has taken reasonable steps to prevent unauthorized access to that information.
5. Termination of Use
You agree that ActFax Communication may, in its sole discretion, at any time terminate your access
to the Site and any account(s) you may have in connection with the Site. Access to the
Site may be monitored by ActFax Communication.
6. Third Party Web Sites, Content, Products and Services
The Site provides links to Web sites and access to content, products and services from
third parties, including users, advertisers, affiliates and sponsors of the Site. You
agree that ActFax Communication is not responsible for the availability of, and content provided on,
third party Web sites. You should refer to the policies posted by other Web sites
regarding privacy and other topics before you use them. You agree that ActFax Communication is not
responsible for third party content accessible through the Site, including opinions,
advice, statements and advertisements, and understand that you bear all risks associated
with the use of such content. If you choose to purchase any products or services from a
third party, your relationship is directly with the third party. You agree that ActFax Communicationis not responsible for: (a) the quality of third party products or services; and (b)
fulfilling any of the terms of your agreement with the seller, including delivery of
products or services and warranty obligations related to purchased products or services.
You agree that ActFax Communication is not responsible for any loss or damage of any sort you may
incur from dealing with any third party.
7. Disclaimer
EXCEPT WHERE EXPRESSLY PROVIDED OTHERWISE, THE SITE, AND ALL CONTENT, MATERIALS, INFORMATION,
SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS AND SERVICES PROVIDED ON THE SITE, ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE"
BASIS. ACTFAX COMMUNICATION EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED,
INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR
PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. ACTFAX COMMUNICATION MAKES NO WARRANTY THAT: (A) THE SITE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS;
(B) THE SITE WILL BE AVAILABLE ON AN UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, OR ERROR-FREE BASIS; (C) THE
RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF THE SITE OR ANY SERVICES OFFERED THROUGH THE SITE
WILL BE ACCURATE OR RELIABLE; OR (D) THE QUALITY OF ANY PRODUCTS, SERVICES, INFORMATION, OR OTHER
MATERIAL PURCHASED OR OBTAINED BY YOU THROUGH THE SITE WILL MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS.
ANY CONTENT, MATERIALS, INFORMATION OR SOFTWARE DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE
USE OF THE SITE IS DONE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK. ACTFAX COMMUNICATION SHALL HAVE NO RESPONSIBILITY
FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY
CONTENT, MATERIALS, INFORMATION OR SOFTWARE.
ACTFAX COMMUNICATION RESERVES THE RIGHT TO MAKE CHANGES OR UPDATES TO THE SITE AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE.
8. Limitation of Liability
IN NO EVENT SHALL ACTFAX COMMUNICATION BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR
CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, REVENUE, DATA OR USE, INCURRED BY
YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION IN CONTRACT OR TORT, ARISING FROM YOUR ACCESS
TO, OR USE OF, THE SITE.
SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY. ACCORDINGLY,
SOME OF THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
9. Indemnity
You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless ActFax Communication, its officers, directors, employees
and agents from and against any and all claims, liabilities, damages, losses or expenses,
including reasonable attorneys' fees and costs, arising out of or in any way connected
with your access to or use of the Site.
10. Privacy Policy
ActFax Communication is concerned about your privacy and has developed a policy to address
privacy concerns. You can find the current privacy policy in our Privacy Statement.
11. Note About Children
Minors are not eligible to use the Site, and we ask that they do not submit any
personal information to us.
12. Copyright/Trademark Information
Copyright © 2020, ActFax Communication. All rights reserved.
ActFax is a registered trademark of ActFax Communication. Other names appearing
on the Site may be trademarks of their respective owners.
13. Contact Information
If you have any questions regarding these Terms of Use, please contact
ActFax Communication at office@actfax.com.
Copyright © 1999-2020 by ActFax Communication-Software GmbH. All rights reserved.
ActFax and ActFax product names are trademarks or registered trademarks of ActFax Communication.
All other product names and services may be trademarks or service marks of their respective owners.
